inkybee.com 2019-06-15

# Privacy policy

### Inkybee Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”)

For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the **Act** ), the data controller is Inkybee (and ‘we’, ‘our’ and ‘us’).

Definitions

In this Privacy Policy:

**Feedback Information:** means information reported voluntarily to us by users of our services in emails, feedback forms or via the online community forum.

**Information:** means Feedback Information, Personal Information and Passive Information.

**Passive Information:** means the information described in clause 2.3 of this Agreement.

**Personal Information:** means all private or personal information provided to us as described in clause 2.1 of this Agreement.

### 1\. Our Commitment to your Privacy.

1.1 We value our relationship with you and respect your right to privacy. We are committed to protecting the confidentiality and security of your Information. We will not share private information about you with third parties without your consent, except for the specific purposes described below.

1.2 This Privacy Policy describes the Information we gather, how we use and safeguard Information and the circumstances under which we may share it I. Please also refer to the Terms and Conditions of Use Agreement (Terms and Conditions of Use). The definitions used in the Terms and Conditions of Use apply to the Privacy Policy. If you are no longer a customer, our Privacy Policy continues to apply to you.

1.3 This Privacy Policy applies solely to Information that is acquired through your use of our websites and/or services. Our websites may contain links that will allow you to access other websites. Linked websites are not under our control and may be subject to a different privacy policy. We accept no responsibility or liability for these other websites.

1.4 By subscribing for our services, you consent to receiving periodic emails to the email address associated with your login details. Subscribers can opt-out of our emails at any time by clicking the “Unsubscribe” link that is present at the very bottom of these emails.

1.5 By using our websites or subscribing for our services, you consent to our collection and use of your Information, in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

### 2\. Information Collected in the Registration Process or through your use of our Websites and/or Services.

2.1 You retain ownership of all data you enter or upload and have ultimate control over who has access to it. You control that access via user accounts that only you can create. It is your responsibility to safeguard the password information and only give it to people you trust. We have no access to user passwords or accounts.

2.1.1 Personal Information: We limit the collection and use of personal information to the minimum required to provide the Inkybee services to you. In order to subscribe for the services, we require that you complete a registration process. This process requests personal information such as name, address, email address, telephone number and other basic contact information. You can view, modify or change your Information within the client account management web page. We do not store credit card details nor do we share customer details with any third parties.

2.1.2 Inkybee stores email addresses as securely as other Personal Information. Your email address will not be passed on to any third party for marketing purposes. However, we may use email addresses to advise clients of service issues and new service offerings.

2.1.3 During the process of performing the services we will also process information in relation to user’s own activities or the activities in relation to a user’s clients. This includes marketing materials such as press releases and target websites and other information such as their Google Analytics API key. For the purposes of this Agreement, this information is treated as Personal Information.

2.2 Feedback Information is used to improve our services. We reserve the right to utilise anonymous Feedback Information for marketing purposes. We will not use any personally identifiable Feedback Information without your explicit consent.

2.3. Passive Information: We collect Passive Information from users of our websites at different points on our websites and through our software. Passive Information is used primarily on an aggregated level to provide you with a better service and for internal resource management. Passive Information is kept strictly confidential and is not shared with third parties, except as provided in this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to use and control the following Passive Information collected:

2.3.1 Our software records general statistical and tracking information while you are accessing the our services, such as date and time of access and time spent using the Inkybee services. Our software transfers this information to our servers, and such information is used exclusively for internal resource management purposes.

2.3.2 We may automatically receive and record information in our server logs from your browser, including the Internet address of your PC (your IP address), your computer’s name, the type and version of your web browser, referrer addresses and other generally-accepted log information. We may also record page views (hit counts) and other general statistical and tracking information, which will be aggregated with that of other users of our websites in order to understand how they are being used.

2.3.3 In order to determine whether your computer is supported by our system, we may collect certain anonymous information about your computer’s configuration. This information is kept strictly confidential and is not shared with third parties, except as provided in this Privacy Policy.

2.3.4 Cookies are small pieces of information that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your browser to enable Inkybee’s system to recognize your browser. Cookies enable us to provide you with a tailored user experience and make it easier for you to use our websites upon future visits. Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default, though you can manually disable the cookies feature of your browser. Please note that if you disable cookies on your computer, some parts of our websites may not function properly.

2.3.5 A ‘referrer’ is the information passed along by a web browser that references the web URL you linked from and is automatically collected by our web server. This information is collected and used by Inkybee to understand which websites refer traffic to our websites and to present appropriate content to our potential customers. Inkybee tabulates referrer information on an aggregate basis to identify trends and traffic patterns.

### 3\. Uses Made of the Information.

We use the Information held about you to deliver services to you in the most effective manner and to carry out all obligations arising as a result of the provision of the services such as billing, upgrades and account maintenance.

### 4\. Limited Circumstances where we are required to Disclose your Information.

4.1 In general, except as provided in this Privacy Policy, we will not sell, rent, trade or otherwise transfer any of your Information to any unaffiliated third parties without your express consent or allowing you to decline to permit the disclosure. There are, however, some limited circumstances in which we may need to disclose Information about a user without express consent, including, but not limited to, the circumstances set forth below:

4.1.1 Inkybee Vendors: We may employ other companies to perform functions on our behalf, such as processing credit card payments, fulfilling orders, providing customer service, sending print and electronic mail, or other functions necessary to our business. In order to allow these companies to fulfill their obligations, we may need to share your Information with them. However, we will provide these companies with only that Information necessary to perform their functions on our behalf, and we will not allow them to use your Information for any other purpose.

4.1.2 Protection of Rights: We may reveal your Information to lawyers or law enforcement officials if we believe that you have harmed or interfered (or will imminently harm or interfere) with other users of our websites or anyone else or violating (either intentionally or unintentionally) our Terms and Conditions of Use or infringing any of Inkybee’s legal rights, or harming the legal rights, property, or health or safety of any other person.

4.1.3 Required by Law: Inkybee will reveal your Information, to the extent we reasonably believe we are required to do so by law. If we receive legal process calling for the disclosure of any of your Information, we will attempt to notify you via the email address you supplied during registration within a reasonable period of time before we respond to the request, unless such notification is not permitted.

4.1.4 Asset Transfer: We shall be entitled to transfer the Information to a third party in connection with a transaction involving a transfer of some or all of the business and assets relating to the websites and/or services or a business in connection with which such Information is maintained.

### 5\. Security of Your Information.

5.1 Our employees are required to protect the confidentiality of your Information and to comply with our established policies. Authorised employees may only access Information in order to fulfill their given duties. We also maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect your Information which comply with all applicable laws.

5.2 Accordingly, we have put in place security systems designed to prevent unauthorised disclosure of your Information. These systems are structured to deter and prevent hackers and others from accessing your Information. Due to the nature of Internet communications and evolving technologies, however, we cannot provide, and disclaim, assurance that your Information will remain free from loss, misuse, or alteration by third parties who, despite our efforts, obtain unauthorised access.

### 6\. Where we Store the Information.

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area (‘EEA”). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. Inkybee will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

### 7\. Your Rights.

You have the right to request a copy of personal information we hold about you. To do this, simply write to us or send us an email – you’ll find our contact details here. We may charge you £10 for providing this information to cover our administration costs. You may unsubscribe from our email newsletter at any time by emailing or writing to us. To provide the highest level of customer service we need accurate customer information. You can help by informing us whenever your circumstances change. You can ask us to correct incorrect personal information about you by writing to or emailing us. You can find detailed information about your rights under UK Data Protection legislation on the UK Information Commissioner’s website at [www.ico.gov.uk](http://www.ico.gov.uk/).

### 8\. Our Right to Modify or Change this Privacy Policy.

Inkybee reserves the right to change or modify this Privacy Policy from time to time, or to terminate this Privacy Policy. We will post notice of the new policy using the Privacy Policy links on our websites. Your use of our websites following any such change constitutes your agreement to follow and be bound by the Privacy Policy, as changed. If we make any significant changes regarding disclosure of your Information to third parties, we will attempt to notify you prior to the date the modified policy takes effect.

Any questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy should be addressed to [support@inkybee.com](mailto:support@inkybee.com).
